[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A fierce eating machine, this creature is one of the few non-humans to appear on AFI\u2019s list of the top movie villains, at # 18.", "correct_answer": "The Shark from Jaws", "incorrect_answers": ["Hal 9000 in 2001: A Space Odyssey", "Terminator from The Terminator", "Alien from Aliens"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following statements is true about ants eyes and eyesight?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["The eyesight of most ants ranges from poor to average, and a number of species that live underground are completely blind.", "Ants have compound eyes which consist of multiple small lenses.", "Ants have three simple eyes called ocelli on the top of their heads that detect light levels and polarization"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sound travels one mile in five seconds in the air, and one mile in how many seconds under water?", "correct_answer": "one second", "incorrect_answers": ["ten seconds", "five seconds", "fifteen seconds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which bathroom item is also a communication protocol?", "correct_answer": "SOAP", "incorrect_answers": ["BRUSH", "GEL", "COMB"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the average height of a stegosaurus?", "correct_answer": "9 feet (2.7 m)", "incorrect_answers": ["8 feet (2.4 m)", "10 feet (3 m)", "12 feet (12.6 m)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these will our Sun eventually become?", "correct_answer": "Planetary Nebula", "incorrect_answers": ["Neutron Star", "Black Hole", "Emission Nebula"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "An effective minimum price imposed by the government, called price floor in economics, is usually expected to result in what?", "correct_answer": "Surplus", "incorrect_answers": ["Increased demand", "Decreased supply", "Shortage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which part of the Earth is made up of iron mixed with nickel?", "correct_answer": "The outer core", "incorrect_answers": ["The asthenosphere", "The inner core", "The mantle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The irrational constant pi is not only popular in the math science, but also in science fiction. Which of these TV series has an episode, in which pi plays a significant role?", "correct_answer": "Star Trek", "incorrect_answers": ["Lost in Space", "Firefly", "The X-Files"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was the local shooting done for the movie Jaws?", "correct_answer": "Marthas Vineyard, Massachusetts", "incorrect_answers": ["Brooklyn, New York", "New Jersey", "Junction City, Kansas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The scene from Dirty Dancing where Johnny is running his hand down Babys arm and side had to be re-shot many times because the director did not like the way Jennifer was laughing.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the first Copper Penny created?", "correct_answer": "1792", "incorrect_answers": ["1794", "1795", "1793"]}]